(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) My name is Gopalakrishnan. I am from Tambaram, Chennai.
I have been working with him for the last one and a half years.
I was diagnosed with HBVNC at the age of 13-13.5 in 3 months.
I went to his award function and saw that he wanted to win an award next time.
I followed his instructions.
I was cured in 3 months.
My mother and my sister had the same type of diabetes.
I have done a reversal for my sister.
I am trying for my mother now.
We are very happy to hear this.
First of all, you have won an award.
We are very happy about that.
Congratulations from our side.
Did you expect this day to come in your life?
Yes, I did.
I got the courage when I saw Dr. Farmer.
I got the courage at the award function.
I was very eager to win the award.
I think it is better to do a reversal for my mother and sister.
I am going to divide this journey into two parts.
Before joining My Health School and after joining.
Before joining, you have faced many challenges.
After joining, you have faced many changes.
Tell us about those changes.
Before joining, I had a food habit.
I didn't know how to eat properly.
I used to eat idly, dosa and other items.
I don't eat much in the morning.
I don't eat until 12 o'clock because of fasting.
I eat a lot in the afternoon.
I eat a lot in the evening.
I eat less in the evening.
I don't have any sugar in my diet.
I feel like my body is full of sugar.
I am very active.
I will take this to at least 10 members.
Your health coach has supported you.
What is her name and a few words about her?
She is Mahalakshmi.
She supported me a lot.
She replied to my messages on WhatsApp.
She gave me a solution.
She supported me a lot.
I don't lack anything.
Many people want to join.
But for some reasons, they are hesitant to join.
They want to reverse their diabetes.
But they are hesitant to join.
What advice do you have for them?
When you join for the first time,
you have to think about what you want to do.
You have to think about what you want to do.
Only if you think about it, you can do it.
Your health coach will give you the support you need.
Many people have joined.
They are your junior batches.
What do you want to say to them?
Once you join,
you will get a sense of achievement.
You will get it in a month or two.
I got it too.
Other than that,
those who have joined,
they can definitely get this award.
When you saw the reverse report,
you got a sense of achievement.
You got a sense of achievement.
Tell us about that.
I told my mother first.
I told my mother and my family.
I was happy.
When I made such habits,
they were the ones who made fun of me.
They said that I shouldn't do this.
I should go for a tablet.
I have changed them.
I am very happy about that.
We are very happy to hear that
you are walking on the path of success.
We are very happy that
we are a part of that success.
If you had to say a word to him,
what would you say?
I would say that
he is a gift from God.
I don't have the mind to listen to anyone.
When I saw his video,
I didn't know what he had.
I didn't know what he was like.
I had a mindset that I should listen to him.
Super sir.
We are very happy to hear that
your family has come out of this.
You should also follow this.
You should definitely come out of this.
I would like to say this to many more people.
Thank you so much sir.
Thank you.